[
    {
        "option1": "Have not you gone at home yet ?",
        "option2": "Have not you gone home yet ?",
        "option3": "Not you have gone to home yet ?",
        "option4": "Not yet you gone home ?",
        "question": "তুমি এখনো বাড়িতে যাও নি ?",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "You never go to my house.",
        "option2": "You never went to my house.",
        "option3": "You never went my house.",
        "option4": "You never have went to my house.",
        "question": "তুমি কখনো আমার বাড়ি যাও নি",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Now we not playing.",
        "option2": "Now we not are playing.",
        "option3": "We are not playing now.",
        "option4": "We are not play now.",
        "question": "আমরা এখন খেলছি না",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "We not played today.",
        "option2": "We have not played today.",
        "option3": "We not have played today.",
        "option4": "We played not today.",
        "question": "আমরা আজ খেলি নি",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "We not played yesterday.",
        "option2": "We did not played yesterday.",
        "option3": "We have not played yesterday.",
        "option4": "We did not play yesterday.",
        "question": " আমরা কাল খেলি নি",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Are you do this work ?",
        "option2": "Are you doing this work ?",
        "option3": "Are you working this work ?",
        "option4": "Are you work this work ?",
        "question": "তুমি কি এই কাজটা করছ ?",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Are they not do the work ?",
        "option2": "Are the work not they doing ?",
        "option3": "Are they not doing the work ?",
        "option4": "Have they not doing the work ?",
        "question": "তারা কি কাজটা করছে না ?",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Have Salil and Moktar play with together ?",
        "option2": "Has Salil and Moktar played with together ?",
        "option3": "Has played together Salil and Moktar ?",
        "option4": "Have Salil and Moktar played together ?",
        "question": "সলিল আর মোক্তার কি একসঙ্গে খেলেছে ?",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Have Salil and Moktar not played together ?",
        "option2": "Are Salil and Moktar have not played together ?",
        "option3": "Have Salil and Moktar not play together ?",
        "option4": "Are Salil and Moktar not played together ?",
        "question": "সলিল আর মোক্তার কি একসঙ্গে খেলে নি ?",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Did king Puru won against Alexander ?",
        "option2": "Did king Puru win against Alexander ?",
        "option3": "Have king Puru won against Alexander ?",
        "option4": "Are king Puru won against Alexander ?",
        "question": "রাজা পুরু আলেকজাণ্ডারের বিরুদ্ধে কি জিতেছিলেন ?",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "King Puru did not win against Alexander ?",
        "option2": "Did win king Puru against Alexander ?",
        "option3": "Did king Puru not won against Alexander ?",
        "option4": "Did king Puru not win against Alexander ?",
        "question": " রাজা পুরু আলেকজাণ্ডারের বিরুদ্ধে কি জেতেন নি ?",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I swim can.",
        "option2": "I know swim.",
        "option3": "I can swim.",
        "option4": "I can cut swim.",
        "question": " আমি সাঁতার কাটতে পারি",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "He can swim in the sea today.",
        "option2": "He may swim on the sea today.",
        "option3": "He may swim in the sea today.",
        "option4": "He can swim on the sea today.",
        "question": "সে আজ সমুদ্রে সাঁতার কাটতেও পারে",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]